<resources>
    <string-array name="category_of_hotels">
        <item>youth-hostel</item>
        <item>5star</item>
        <item>4star</item>
        <item>3star</item>
        <item>Boutique</item>
        <item>7star</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="places_options">
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Canada</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>New Zealand</item>
        <item>Dubai</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>UK</item>
        <item>France</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>Switzerland</item>
        <item>Thailand</item>
        <item>Singapore</item>
        <item>Malaysia</item>
        <item>Ireland</item>
        <item>Norway</item>
        <item>Sweden</item>
        <item>Bhutan</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Europe (south)</item>
        <item>Europe (north)</item>
        <item>Europe (custom)</item>
        <item>Europe (east)</item>
        <item>Russia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="app_name">Pristine Travels</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_about_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_custom__itinerary">Customize your Itinerary</string>
    <string name="title_activity_packages_available">Popular Packages</string>
    <string name= "help_content">Don\'t worry if you don\'t understand what\'s happening here. Except for packing your bags,
        we are here to help you all the way. Here\'s what you need to do\n
        1. Fill in the country/continent with the duration, people travelling,along with your approximate budget.\n
        2. Add ages of the children by separating them with a space. (Eg. for ages 12,14,9 write : 12 14 9
        3. Choose specific destinations you want to visit, along with dates. (Eg - Barcelona 26/12/18 - 28/12/18)\n
        4. Specify hotel category,add activities you wish to include. We will recommend any field left empty.\n
        5. Just click on "Request Itinerary" and choose any email client which will send us the details of your choices.\n
        Note - We will get back to you after receiving your mail,as soon as we can, and Hey! thanks for contacting us.
    </string>
    <string name="Australia_pack">Day 00 - Depart for Perth.\n
Bon Voyage! Embark on your overnight flight to Australia.\n\n
Day 01 - Welcome to Perth\n
Tour Manager / Local Representative will meet you outside the arrival hall aftercustoms. Proceed to your hotel, enjoy Swan River Cruise from Perth to port of Fremantle, in which the captain points out Perth’s Bell Tower, Swan Brewery, Kings Park and many more. Spend some time to explore Fremantle, the port city. (Standard
check in at 1400hr). Overnight in Gold coast.\n\n
Day 02 - Discover Rottnest Island with 90 mins Coach Tour and Lunch.Today visit Rottnest island on ferry and explore the island on a 90 minute coach tour of the island.Overnight in Perth.\n\n
Day 03 - Pinnacles Desert with 4WD sand dune adventure – Picnic lunch.Today enjoy 4WD Sand Dune Adventure, and visit Caversham Wildlife park and get an opportunity to see koalas, wombats and Kangaroos close up, try hand on Sand Boarding. Enjoy a picnic lunch at the coastal town of Cervantes.Take a guided walk through the Pinnacles desert and its limestone pillars. Overnight in Gold coast.\n\n
Day 04 - (FLIGHT TO Adelaide)\n
Adelaide city tour, On arrival in Adelaide enjoy Adelaide city tour- Classic Victoria Square, Grand boulevard of King William Street, Beehive Corner, the Terrace, Elegant Parliament House, State Library, Trinity Church, Adelaide’s oldest church, Trendy Hutt Street,
photo stop at Adelaide Oval ground. Overnight in Adelaide\n\n
Day 05 - Free day at leisure - Optional Hot Air Ballooning at Barossa Valley with Winery breakfast OR Kangaroo Island. This morning you have an option to go for hot air ballooning at Barossa Valley or visit
to Kangaroo Island by ferry or you can spend your free day to explore the city on your own. Overnight in Adelaide.\n\n
Day 06 - (FLIGHT TO MELBOURNE)\n
Visit Eureka Sky Deck. On arrival into Melbourne transfer to Eureka Sky Deck. Overnight in Melbourne.\n\nPRICE : 1.5 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability \n</string>
    <string name="New_Zealand_pack">Day 1 - Arrive Auckland \n
On arrival, at the arrival hall, turn right towards rental car counters, complete hiring formalities and pick up your rental car and proceed to
your hotel. There will be no assistance at the airport. Later in the evening proceed for Sky Tower Auckland Tour. Visit to the 186 meter Main
Observation Level, 182 metre Sky Lounge caf and bar and 220 meter Sky Deck. Opening hours 7 days Sunday - Thursday 8.30am to
10.30pm, Friday and Saturday 8.30am - 11.30pm. Reporting time: 05PM\n\n
Day 2 - Auckland - Tauranga\n
At Leisure
Depart Auckland and travel south to the city of Tauranga. (192kms, 2hrs 40mins approx.)\n\n
Day 3 - Today after breakfast you have day at leisure. Later enjoy a beautiful private Tour in the local area in a V8 Trike bike Summer Hills, McLaren Falls, Minden Lookout.\n\n
Day 4 - Today, depart Tauranga and travel south to the thermal resort of Rotorua. (65kms, 1hr 10mins approx.) On arrival at Rotorua, proceed for Whakarewarewa The Living Thermal Village Tour. Our authentic culture is what makes Te Whakarewarewa such a unique attraction. Be a part of our living legacy as you experience living Maori traditions. Discover the unique geothermal landscape of Te Whakarewarewa Valley. Being the only living geothermal Maori village, we are gifted with geothermal vents that provide a life-giving energy resource. See our
boiling hot pools and bubbling mud, and learn how our residents utilise and respect the ever-changing forces beneath our land. The Performance Each performance includes Waiata (songs) of our history, Patere (rhythmic chants), stick games, poi dancing, and the world
famous HAKA war challenge. There is also a voluntary audience participation section, where you will learn the basics of Maori performance art and expand your Te Reo vocabulary.\n\n
Day 5 - Experience the real Middle-earth with a visit to the Hobbiton Movie Set, the bucolicsetting for The Shire that featured in the Peter Jackson directed films, The Lord of the Rings. Your tour starts with a drive through the picturesque 1,250 acre sheep farm with spectacular views across to the Kaimai Ranges. Your guide will escort you through the ten acre site recounting fascinating details of how the Hobbiton set was created. The Hobbit holes, Green Dragon Inn, Mill and other structures created for The Lord of the Rings and The Hobbit films can be viewed and you will see how this beautiful piece of Waikato farmland was transformed into The Shire from Middle-earth. (Reporting time 10AM)\n\n
Day 6 - Rotorua - Queenstown \n
At Leisure
Drive to Rotorua airport, park your car at Hertz parking slot. Drop the keys at Hertz counter located inside the terminal building. Fly from Rotorua to Queenstown (Flight not Included) Make your way to the rental car branch at the Queenstown Airport to complete hiring formalities and pick up your rental car.\n\n
Day 7 - Today you have full day at leisure. You may enjoy the ice cream at Mrs Jones Fruit Stall.\n\n
Day 8 - Depart Queenstown this morning for the scenic and short journey to Te Anau. (175 kms 2hrs 30mins. approx.) Later proceed for Skyline Queenstown Combo Gondola and 1 Luge ride tour. Marvel at the stunning views as you ride the Skyline Queenstown Gondola the steepest cable car lift in the Southern Hemisphere! Sit back and relax as the best views in the region unfold before your eyes and the Gondola carries you 450 metres above Queenstown and Lake Wakatipu to the top of Bob's Peak. En route you will enjoy a spectacular 220 degree panorama, with breath taking views of Coronet Peak, The Remarkables, Walter Peak, Cecil Peak and over Queenstown. On arrival the
purpose built viewing platforms and outdoor terraces provide great photo opportunities. Combine your Gondola experience with the Luge ride. The Luge is a thrilling ride for all ages and abilities. Jump on your specialised Luge cart, select your track, then take control as you
zoom down the Luge. Then catch the Luge chairlift back to the start zone and do it all over again once is never enough! The Scenic track is a leisurely ride with gentle gradient, easy bends, tunnels and dips. The Advanced track has a steeper gradient and is a more adventurous
ride with the thrill of banked corners, tunnels, dippers and cuttings.\n\n
Day 9 - Leave Te Anau this morning and travel East through historical Central Otago to the Scottish influenced city of Kaka Point (290 kms 4hrs
15mins. approx.)\n\n
Day 10 - Depart Kaka Point and travel south along the east coast to reach the garden city of Christchurch. (180km, 2hrs 30mins approx) Later proceed to Cadbury World Dunedin Full Tour. The Full Tour last for approximately 75 minutes. This tour includes the self guided experience through the Cadbury World Visitor Centre where you can learn about the history of chocolate since its discovery, see how Cadbury chocolate has evolved over the years, view popular Cadbury television advertisements and miniature Cadbury truck replicas, and learn about where Cadbury operates all over the world. Cadbury World is open 7 days a week, with tours running from 9am to 3.15pm (Reporting Time 10:00 AM)\n\n
Day 11 - Dunedin - Christchurch\n
At Leisure
Travel north from the Scottish influenced city Dunedin towards historic Oamaru with it's impressive stone buildings. Then follow the coastal
road to the port city of Timaru and continue your journey across the Canterbury Plains before reaching Christchurch.(365 kms, 5hrs 15mins.
approx.)\n\n
Day 12 - Christchurch - Departure \n
Today after breakfast proceed to airport, drop your car at the counter. Good days never comes to an end, hope you enjoy your holidays in New Zealand. Tour Concludes!\n\n
    \nPRICE : 2.3 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability</string>
    <string name="America1_pack">
        Day 1 - Welcome to Los Angeles\n
Bon Voyage! Today, your fun-filled tour of the United States of America begins. On
arrival at Los Angeles, your friendly Thomas Cook tour manager will be waiting
outside the baggage hall to welcome and transfer you to your hotel. The rest of the
day is free for you to experience the pulse of this amazing city on your own.\n\n
Day 2 - Visit Universal Studios Hollywood. Visit Hollywood Boulevard. \n
After breakfast, become a part of Hollywood magic as you visit Universal studios, the work place of Hollywood’s biggest and most glamorous stars. Go behind the scenes on the legendry studio tram tour to explore Hollywood’s most famous and world’s largest working movie studio. From magical spells to magical creatures, from dark villains to daring heroes, experience it all at the newly opened ‘Wizarding World of Harry Potter’. Enjoy breathtaking rides like Transformers 3D, Jurassic park, Revenge of the Mummy and many more. Later this evening proceed for an orientation tour of Los Angeles. Visit the Main Street in Hollywood-“Hollywood Boulevard” where you get a pulse of the city. See the Dolby Theatre which hosts the annual academy awardsthe Oscars and Walk along the Hollywood Walk of Fame. Also see the TCL Chinese
theatre- one of the oldest theatre in Hollywood. Drive along the famous Sunset Strip and Beverly Hills area; also see the famous Beverly Wilshire hotel. Tonight enjoy dinner at an Indian Restaurant. Overnight in Los Angeles.\n\n
Day 3 - Onto The Dazzling City of Las Vegas.\n
After breakfast, drive to Las Vegas - the gambling capital of the world. Lunch will be provided. On arrival, check-in to your hotel. Later you can explore the grandeur of your own hotel or you can just walk along the Las Vegas Boulevard - the main street. Tonight enjoy dinner at a local Indian restaurant. Overnight in Las Vegas.\n\n
Day 4 - Tour to Grand Canyon includes a panoramic or scenic flying adventure to the remote wilderness of the magnificent Grand Canyon. Later this evening drive
past the famous themed hotels of Las Vegas in a luxurious Limousine. After dinner at an Indian restaurant, proceed for an exciting Fremont Street experience. Overnight
in Las Vegas.\n\n
Day 5- Flight to San Francisco - Enjoy Bay Cruise.\n
After breakfast/boxed breakfast, proceed to the airport for your flight to San Francisco. Lunch will be provided, enjoy an exciting Bay Cruise as you sail past the
San Francisco skyline and the Golden Gate Bridge. Cruise around the infamous island of Alcatraz, formerly a maximum security minimum privileges prison. This evening
enjoy dinner at an Indian restaurant, later check-in into your hotel. Overnight in San Francisco / Oakland.\n\n
Day 6 - Guided City Tour of San Francisco. Visit Sausalito.\n
See famous attractions like Civic Centre, Union Square, Lombard Street, Golden Gate Park and Park Presidio. Also visit the Twin Peaks, the highest vista point of the city. Lunch will be provided. Proceed to Sausalito. The rest of the day is at leisure to explore the city on your own. You could also shop at Market Street or look for good bargains around Union Square. Tonight, enjoy Indian dinner. Overnight in San Francisco / Oakland.\n\n
Day 7 - Flight to Buffalo. Visit Niagara Falls by Night.\n
After breakfast/boxed breakfast check-out and proceed to the airport for your flight to Buffalo, visit the city of Niagara Falls - one of the natural wonders of the world. On arrival, check-in to your hotel. Tonight, after Indian dinner at the restaurant, we proceed to view the magnificent falls by night. Overnight in Niagara.\n\n
Day 8 - Enjoy, Maid of the Mist boat ride at the Niagara Falls.\n
After breakfast, embark on the unforgettable boat ride aboard the world famous Maid of The Mist, which gives you a breathtaking view of the cascading waters of this majestic waterfall. (Due to weather conditions, this ride usually operates after the 2nd week of May. We offer the ‘View Mobile Tram Ride’ instead, for all tourists visiting the falls prior to the commencement of this ride). Lunch will be provided. Later proceed to Washington D.C. – Capital of United States of America. After Dinner at an Indian restaurant; proceed to hotel for check in. Overnight in Washington, D.C.\n\n
Day 9 - Guided City Tour of Washington DC, Visit to Smithsonian National Natural History Museum\n
After breakfast, we proceed on a guided sightseeing tour of this historic city. Visit the U.S. Capitol hill; get a memorable photo in front of the White House, the residence of the President of USA; see the Korean and Lincoln memorials and the beautiful WWII memorial and many more sights on your city tour. We then visit the Smithsonian National Natural History Museum, one of the most visited museums in the world. Later enjoy Lunch and proceed to New York City. Tonight, enjoy Indian dinner and check-in into your hotel. Overnight in Manhattan, New York.\n\n
Day 10 - Visit the Statue of Liberty, Guided City tour of New York City, One World Trade Centre Observatory\n
After breakfast proceed for your scenic boat cruise to the Liberty Island for a close up view of “The Statue of Liberty”. After lunch, proceed on a guided city tour of Manhattan, drive past Brooklyn and Manhattan Bridges, United Nations Headquarters,Trump Towers, Central Park and the Times Square - The Heart of the Entertainment District. Later go whizzing to the observatory of the tallest building in the western hemisphere – One World Trade Centre in the Sky pod elevators, amongst the fastest in the world. Get unforgettable 360degree views of the city from the Observatory. Next, it’s time to experience New York’s iconic landmark, the Times Square, by night. Tonight enjoy Indian dinner. Overnight in Manhattan, New York.\n\n
Day 11 - Atlanta, the Olympic city of USA\n
Today, after breakfast/box breakfast, proceed to the airport for your flight to Atlanta. The City nicknamed as “The Olympic City of USA”. After arrival, proceed to the hotel for check-in. This evening, enjoy dinner at an Indian restaurant. Overnight in Atlanta.\n\n
Day 12 - Visit the CNN Centre, Enjoy the World of Coca Cola and Experience the Georgia Aquarium.\n
Day 13 - Guided city tour and Visit Swami Narayan Temple. Free time for Shopping.\n
After breakfast, proceed for a Guided city tour of Atlanta that includes the most interesting stops such as the Martin Luther King Jr. National Historical Park. Enjoy a drive through the Buckhed neighborhood to view stately mansions. Visit Ebenezer Baptist Church and other places within the Martin Luther King Jr. National Historical Park. Next we Visit the BAPS Shri Swaminarayan Mandir a traditional Hindu mandir, or place of worship, and is the largest mandir of its kind outside of India. The mandir is made of 34,450 pieces of hand-carved Italian marble, Turkish Limestone and Indian pink sandstone. Later, we take you to the most famous shopping centre of Atlanta the Phipps Plaza and Lenox Mall. Enjoy dinner at an Indian restaurant. Overnight in Atlanta\n\n
Day 14 - Tour Ends, After breakfast proceed to the Airport.\n\n
        \nPRICE : 3.1 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability
    </string>
    <string name="Europe1_pack">4 COUNTRIES, 8 PLACES, 11 DAYS\n\n
        Schedule : \n
                  Day 0 : We leave for Paris ( Friday )\n\t
                  Day 1 : We reach Paris 4 : 35\n\t\t
                              Eiffel tower the same day.\n
                  Day 2 : We see two of the aforementioned 4 places. If time permits, we see 3.\n\t
                                   The Louvre\n\t\t
                                   Notre Dame\n\t\t
                                   Basilique du Sacré-Coeur\n\t\t
                                   Pont Alexandre ||| Bridge \n\t\t
                                   Night train to Chamonix ( Small Village )\n
                  Day 3 : Day in Chamonix, climb the MOnt. Blanc mountain.
                                   Stay there for the night, \n
                  Day 4 : Roam around the town ,around noon leave for Geneva
                                  reach there in less than 3 hours. If exhausted, we have a rest day, or we go and roam around the city,\n
                  Day 5 : Around 4 we leave for Milan, stay in Milan\n
                  Day 6 : In Milan, we roam around the city, We stay the night\n
                  Day 7 : Morning train to Cinque terre, Roam around the city , staying there for the night.\n
                  Day 8 : Leave for  Maranello in the morning. Look at the museums. At night, Train to Venice\n
                  Day 9 : Venice, at night, we take a train to Prague\n
                  Day 10 : Stay at Prague .Flight back home at night \n
        \nPRICE : 1.7 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability\n
</string>
    <string name="Europe2_pack">
4 COUNTRIES,6 PLACES, 7 NIGHTS \n\n
Schedule - \n
Day 1 - Flight to Paris, Dinner at Restaurant and check in to the hotel.\n
Day 2 - Guided City Tour, includes \n
\t\t1] Alexander Bridge\n
\t\t2] Arc De Triumph\n
\t\t3] Concorde Square\n
\t\t4] Opera House\n
\t\t5] Louvre\n
\t\t5] Eiffel Tower\n
Afternoon trip to Disneyland Paris, evening dinner followed by the famous Lido Show at night.\n
Day 3 - Check out, train to Brussels. City tour includes \n
\t\t1] Mini-Europe\n
\t\t2] Manneken Pis Statue\n
\t\t3] Grand Palace\n
Day 4 - Travel to Cologne, visit the Cologne Cathedral and board the scenic Rhine river cruise in the evening.\n
Day 5 - Tour to Heidelberg, heart of Black Forest. Evening drive to Switzerland, arrave at Schaffhausen. view the Rhine Falls there. \n
Day 6 - Travel to Jungfraujoch ( highest Railway station of Europe ). Visit includes - \n
\t\t1] Ice Palace\n
\t\t2] Sphinx Observatory Deck\n
\t\t3] Bernese Oberland Mountains\n
Day 7 - Visit Mt. Titlis and Lucerne. Rotair ( Rotating Cable car ride included ). Cliff Walk ( Latest Attraction ).\n
Day 8 - Flight back home.
        \nPRICE : 2.2 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability
    </string>
    <string name="UK_pack">Day 1 - ARRIVE IN LONDON, ENGLAND\n
Welcome to London! After checking into your hotel and afternoon at leisure, we recommend our optional Taste of London excursion with dinner, followed by a guided illuminations cruise on the Thames River.\n\n
Day 2 - LONDON-STONEHENGE-BATH-NEWPORT, WALES\n
Sightseeing, Try to unravel the mystery of prehistoric STONEHENGE. Explore the visitor center with its imaginative exhibitions, then admire the magnificence of the monument up close. At the elegant Georgian city of Bath, see the amazing excavations of the ROMAN BATHS. Then, cross the Severn River for a late-afternoon arrival in Wales. Enjoy a welcome dinner at your hotel.\n\n
Day 3 - NEWPORT-CARDIFF-WATERFORD, IRELAND\n
A morning orientation drive in the Welsh capital features all the major attractions. Take a guided tour of Cardiff Castle, and discover its history of invasions,abductions, and conflicts over the past 2,000 years. Continue along the South Wales coast to Pembroke, where your FERRY will be waiting. Cross St. George Channel to Rosslare on the Emerald Isle and proceed to Waterford, a stronghold founded by the Danish Vikings in 853. After dinner this evening, enjoy an IRISH COFFEE DEMONSTRATION.\n\n
Day 4 - WATERFORD-KILKENNY-DUBLIN\n
This morning, enjoy a guided tour of the HOUSE OF WATERFORD CRYSTAL, then travel on to Kilkenny, one of Irelands prettiest towns with medieval cobblestones and Old-World charm. Visit magnificent KILKENNY CASTLE, which overlooks the Nore River and has guarded this important river crossing for more than 900 years. The gardens, with extensive woodland paths, rose garden, and ornamental lake, create the setting for a beautiful stroll. On arrival in Dublin, top the day with an optional Irish cabaret evening including dinner, dance, song,and laughter.\n\n
Day 5 - DUBLIN \n
An orientation drive in Irelands capital city includes statue-lined O\'Connell Street, elegant Georgian squares, St. Patrick\'s Cathedral, and Oscar Wilde\'s Trinity College. The afternoon is at leisure for you to explore this vibrant city. Tonight, maybe take in an optional dinner outing to the Guinness Storehouse.\n\n
Day 6 - DUBLIN-BELFAST, NORTHERN-IRELAND-EDINBURGH, SCOTLAND\n
On your way to Northern Ireland, cross the Boyne River, then skirt the Mountains of Mourne. In Belfast, where the Titanic was built, take in the citys vibrant history and view the impressive City Hall. Next, board your FERRY to cross the North Channel to Cairnryan on Scotland's
southwest coast and continue through the scenic Scottish border country to Edinburgh. Tonight, relax and enjoy our optional Scottish evening with Highland dancers, bagpipers, and the Ceremony of the Haggis\n\n
Day 7 - EDINBURGH\n
Morning city sightseeing with a local expert introduces you to the 200-year-old "New Town" and the famous scientists, inventors, and novelists who lived there. In the "Old Town," drive up the narrow Royal Mile to EDINBURGH CASTLE to admire Scotland's Crown Jewels.
The afternoon is free to enjoy the Scottish capital at your own pace. Later, a unique optional excursion: board the former Royal Yacht Britannia, and enjoy dinner at a local restaurant. For departure numbers 0729 through 0819, tickets are included for tonight's performance
of the world-renowned MILITARY TATTOO, a vast spectacle of massed Scottish pipe bands that takes place in an arena on the esplanade of Edinburgh Castle\n\n
Day 8 - EDINBURGH-JEDBURGH-YORK, ENGLAND\n
This morning, drive past the abbey ruins at Jedburgh into wild Northumberland National Park. Later, see a section of Hadrian's Wall, the
Roman coast-to-coast defense against marauding northern tribes. In York, Englands most complete medieval city, stand in awe in front of the great structure of York Minster, then follow your Tour Director through a maze of quaint streets, including the narrow Shambles.\n\n
Day 9 - YORK-STRATFORD-UPON-AVON-LONDON\n
On the last leg of your journey, stop at Stratford-upon-Avon, the fascinating Elizabethan town. Take pictures of Anne Hathaways Cottage, visit SHAKESPEARE'S BIRTHPLACE, and enjoy a light LUNCH. On return to London at about 3:30 pm, a Shownight Theater Evening would be an incredible finale to your vacation.\n\n
Day 10 - LONDON\n
Your vacation ends with breakfast this morning\n\n
        \nPRICE : 2.2 Lakh INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability\n
</string>
    <string name="Singapore_pack">
Day 01: BF at Hotel\n\t
        Arrive  Singapore.\n\t
        on Arrival, Private Transfer to Hotel ORCHARD PARADE with bf , for 04 Nights, on Bed and BF.\n\t
        Nights Safari tour –. Private  Transfers\n
Day 02: BF at Hotel\n\t
        City Tour of Singapore, flyer\n\t
        Gardens by the Bay Tour, inclusive 2 Domes.+ MBS Sky park Private  Transfers.\n
Day 03: BF at Hotel\n\t
        Morning Free\n\t
        Afternoon, Sentosa at Sunset Tour. 1 way Cable Car, Wings of Time-2nd show, Sky and Luge Ride-2way;Images Of Singapore and Madame Tussauds+Sea Aquirium\n
        Day 04: BF at Hotel\n\t
Universal Studios And Trick Eye Museum Combo Ticket inclusive Private  Transfers.\n
Day 05: BF at Hotel,\n\t
        Morning free\n\t
        Late Afternoon, Private Transfer to Singapore Airport, for return flight.
        \nPRICE : 60000 INR per person \n
    Note - Prices subject to availability
    </string>
    <string name="Thailand_pack">
Usage of hotels as per standard hotel policy\n
No service held on date, hence prices may vary, according to availability.
        Day 01 Arrive Bangkok, post immigration transfer to Phuket hotel private coach., check into Phuket Deevana Patong as per standard timing, 1 unit
        Deluxe room( Room area about 24 sq mts) with Bf factored for 3 nights.Evening pick up  for Phuket Fantasea Show, includes hotel pick and drop in shared coach.\n
Day 02 Bf at Hotel.\n\t
        Full day Phi Phi  Island Tour with lunch includes-Royal Jet Cruiser
        hotel pick and drop and excursion in shared boat.(national Park fees of 400 THB per person extra to be settled on spot)\n
Day 03 Bf at Hotel\n\t
            Half day Phuket City tour shared coach\n
Day 04 Bf at hotel.\n\t
        Drop at Phuket  Airport private coach, fly for Bangkok on arrival transfers to Bangkok Hotel Arnoma grand  in private coach.
        1  unit of Junior suite 42  sq mts room area with Bf factored at for 2 nights.\n
Day 05 Bf at Hotel\n\t
              Full day safari world or Dream world tour includes lunch with transfers on shared coach.\n
Day 06 Bf at hotel\n\t
        Entry to Sea life Aquarium and Madame Tussauds. Close to hotel no transfers factored hence.\n\t
        Evening drop at Airport.\n\n
        \nPRICE : 40000 INR per person
Includes:\n
Accommodation for 5 nights with Bf\n
Airport Pick and Drop in private.\n
Sightseeing as mentioned\n
    Note - Prices subject to availability</string>
    <string name="title_layout_help">Help\'s here</string>
    <string name="number_of_adults">No. of Adults</string>
    <string name="rooms_required">Rooms required</string>
    <string name="starting_date">Starting Date -</string>
    <string name = "hint_d">Child(ren) ages (seperate multiple with comma)</string>
    <string name="start_date">Starting Date</string>
    <string name="category_of_hotel">  Category of Hotel</string>
    <string name="no_preference">No Preference</string>
    <string name="fill_in_these_fields">Fill in these fields...</string>
    <string name="dets_aboutus">\t We are pleased to introduce ourselves as Customer Focused Total Travel Solution Provider offering wide range of services,
        starting from arranging your journey ticket to designing your international trip.
        We strongly believe in value of time and once we are entrusted with the job,
        you can concentrate on your primary business rather working for your ticket and trip, your hotel booking or even planning your stay.
        \n \t Whether you’re looking for a simple getaway or a unique destination holiday, Pristine Travel can help you plan the perfect trip.
        Take advantage of our full suite of services. From tickets to tours, hotels to honeymoons - we have you covered.</string>
    <string name="dets_air">\t The agency is engaged in offering all kinds of air tickets, be it domestic or international.
        The company holds stocks of almost all-major domestic carriers in India and almost all-international carriers operating out of India.
        The company has on line inventory access to over 100 international and domestic carriers ensuring instant bookings.</string>
    <string name="dets_hotels">\t Pristine help’s you find the perfect place to stay. We have helped countless clients find accommodations
        that meet their needs, from city hotels to beach resorts, from long-term stay options to mountain chalets,
        from luxury stays to value accommodations. So contact us and tell us about what you’re looking for.
\n \t Pristine has online inventory access to a wide range of accommodation options for approximately all locations over the world.
        Thus negotiating the best rates for different categories and instantly booking accommodation for clients.</string>
    <string name="dets_transfer">\t With Pristine you won’t have to worry about getting from point A to point B.
        Whether it’s a flight arrangement, transfers from airport to hotel, Sightseeing or travelling between cities we
        are their take care of all your transportation needs</string>
    <string name="dets_sight">\t Pristine feature sightseeing and orientation in each city so you don’t miss the must see sights. You even personalize your trip by adding the activities and Excursions that will make your Gateway …. Exclusively yours.</string>
    <string name="dets_visa">\t Pristine has a full-fledged department to ensure proper documentation, and quick hassle-free processing of visas to any country. We stock forms and are always updated with consulates. But granting of VISA is at sole discretion of the respective consulate.</string>
    <string name="story_dets">\t We are an IATA approved travel agency based in Kolkata offering you the most comprehensive service
        when it comes to traveling. You can bank upon us for your travel plans.
        We would love to be your travel agent and hear about how we can make your plans exciting and stress-free.\n
        The agency has total staff strength of 15. The team is lead by Rajkumar Sarrof, a director of the company and widely experienced in all fields of travel.
        The agency boasts of trained staff who work relentlessly to give our clients/travelers a smooth, hassle free travel experience.
        \n\tWe, at Pristine Travels Private Limited, are committed to make your every trip a memorable one. Be it a leisure trip within the country
        or abroad with friends and family or a business trip, our impeccable service will make sure that you get the right things at the right moment and at the right price.
        \n\t Since its inception, Team Pristine has been constantly evolving itself to meet the changing challenges and aspirations of the industry
        and strive for better customer services. We are proud to have the maximum repeat business.
        We are grateful to our patrons who have shown tremendous belief in us.
        \n\t Pristine Travel has its network of professional associates across the world providing services to our valuable guests.
        We are specialized in conducting customized tour specially tailored for our guests.</string>
    <string name="contact_dets">\nAddress: Karnani Estate\n209 AJC Bose Road\n5th floor Suite-194\nKolkata-700017\nIATA Accredited\nMember-TAAI and TAFI\n</string>
    <string name ="addr_dets">Karnani Estate\n209 AJC Bose Road\n5th floor Suite-194\nKolkata-700017</string>
    <string name="phone_dets">+91 33 4048 5454</string>
    <string name="email_dets">sarrof@yahoo.co.uk</string>
</resources>

