<resources>
    <string-array name="category_of_hotels">
        <item>youth-hostel</item>
        <item>5star</item>
        <item>4star</item>
        <item>3star</item>
        <item>Boutique</item>
        <item>7star</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="places_options">
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Canada</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>New Zealand</item>
        <item>Dubai</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>UK</item>
        <item>France</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>Switzerland</item>
        <item>Thailand</item>
        <item>Singapore</item>
        <item>Malaysia</item>
        <item>Ireland</item>
        <item>Norway</item>
        <item>Sweden</item>
        <item>Bhutan</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Europe (south)</item>
        <item>Europe (north)</item>
        <item>Europe (custom)</item>
        <item>Europe (east)</item>
        <item>Russia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="app_name">Pristine Travels</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_about_us">Contact_about_us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_custom__itinerary">Custom_Itinerary</string>
    <string name="title_activity_packages_available">Packages_available</string>
    <string name="about_us_text">We are an IATA approved Travel Agency based in Kolkata established in 1997,
        offering the most comprehensive service when it comes to travelling. Our prime products include\n\t\t
        [1]Customized International Tour Packages\n\t\t
        [2]Air Tickets\n\t\t
        [3]Visa Consultancy\nOur office location is - Karnani Estate, 209 AJC Bose Road, 5th floor, Suite 194 Kolkata,West Bengal-700017. If
        you have any queries do contact us. Our working hours are\n
        Monday - Friday : 10 AM - 6 PM\n
        Saturday : 10 AM - 2PM
 </string>
    <string name= "help_content">Don\'t worry if you don\'t understand what\'s happening here. Except for packing your bags,
        we are here to help you all the way. Here\'s what you need to do\n
        1. Fill in the country/continent with the duration, people travelling,along with your approximate budget.\n
        2. Add ages of the children by separating them with a space. (Eg. for ages 12,14,9 write : 12 14 9
        3. Choose specific destinations you want to visit, along with dates. (Eg - Barcelona 26/12/18 - 28/12/18)\n
        4. Specify hotel category,add activities you wish to include. We will recommend any field left empty.\n
        5. Just click on "Request Itinerary" and choose any email client which will send us the details of your choices.\n
        Note - We will get back to you after receiving your mail,as soon as we can, and Hey! thanks for contacting us.
    </string>
    <string name="Australia_pack"></string>
    <string name="New_Zealand_pack"></string>
    <string name="America1_pack"></string>
    <string name="America2_pack"></string>
    <string name="Europe1_pack">4 COUNTRIES, 8 PLACES, 11 DAYS\n\n
        Schedule : \n
                  Day 0 : We leave for Paris ( Friday )\n\t
                  Day 1 : We reach Paris 4 : 35\n\t\t
                              Eiffel tower the same day.\n\t
                  Day 2 : We see two of the aforementioned 4 places. If time permits, we see 3.\n\t
                                   The Louvre\n\t\t
                                   Notre Dame\n\t\t
                                   Basilique du Sacré-Coeur\n\t\t
                                   Pont Alexandre ||| Bridge \n\t\t
                                   Night train to Chamonix ( Small Village )\n\t\t
                  Day 3 : Day in Chamonix, climb the MOnt. Blanc mountain.
                                   Stay there for the night, \n\t
                  Day 4 : Roam around the town ,around noon leave for Geneva
                                  reach there in less than 3 hours. If exhausted, we have a rest day, or we go and roam around the city,\n\t
                  Day 5 : Around 4 we leave for Milan, stay in Milan\n\t
                  Day 6 : In Milan, we roam around the city, We stay the night\n\t
                  Day 7 : Morning train to Cinque terre, Roam around the city , staying there for the night.\n\t
                  Day 8 : Leave for  Maranello in the morning. Look at the museums. At night, Train to Venice\n\t
                  Day 9 : Venice, at night, if possible we take a train to Prague\n\t
                  Day 10 : We stay at Prague Then we take the earliest flight back home, man.\n
Places :\n
\n
1. Chamonix : A small village town in Southern France, amidst the Alps.\n
2. Geneva :  A big city in Western Switzerland\n
3. Milan : One of the very famous cities, of Italy. Must have heard of AC Milan and Inter Milan ( Football clubs )\n
4. Cinque Terre : A small picturesque coastal town, by the beach.\n
5. Maranello : This place doesn\'t need any introduction to you.\n
6. Venice : One of the very beautiful medieval cities of Europe\n
7. Prague : Another big city in the Czech-Republic.
</string>
    <string name="Europe2_pack"></string>
    <string name="UK_pack"></string>
    <string name="Singapore_pack"> 5 days Singapore
PACKAGE cost per person Rs59800/-
Includes :Accommodation with bf for 4 night
Airport transfers and Sights seeing in Private coach
Visa
Air fare additional
No booking has been held, hence prices are subject to change.
5% GST extra.
Day 01: BF at Hotel\n\t
        Arrive  Singapore.\n\t
        on Arrival, Private Transfer to Hotel ORCHARD PARADE with bf , for 04 Nights, on Bed and BF.\n\t
        Nights Safari tour –. Private  Transfers\n
Day 02: BF at Hotel\n\t
        City Tour of Singapore, flyer\n\t
        Gardens by the Bay Tour, inclusive 2 Domes.+ MBS Sky park Private  Transfers.\n
Day 03: BF at Hotel\n\t
        Morning Free\n\t
        Afternoon, Sentosa at Sunset Tour. 1 way Cable Car, Wings of Time-2nd show, Sky and Luge Ride-2way;Images Of Singapore and Madame Tussauds+Sea Aquirium\n
        Day 04: BF at Hotel\n\t
Universal Studios And Trick Eye Museum Combo Ticket inclusive Private  Transfers.\n
Day 05: BF at Hotel,\n\t
        Morning free\n\t
        Late Afternoon, Private Transfer to Singapore Airport, for return flight.
    </string>
    <string name="Dubai_pack"></string>
    <string name="Thailand_pack">6 days Thailand
        Package cost Rs37500 per person\n
5% GST extra\n
Usage of hotels as per standard hotel policy\n
No service held on date, hence prices may vary, according to availability.
        Day 01 Arrive Bangkok, post immigration transfer to Phuket hotel private coach., check into Phuket Deevana Patong as per standard timing, 1 unit
        Deluxe room( Room area about 24 sq mts) with Bf factored for 3 nights.Evening pick up  for Phuket Fantasea Show, includes hotel pick and drop in shared coach.\n
Day 02 Bf at Hotel.\n\t
        Full day Phi Phi  Island Tour with lunch includes-Royal Jet Cruiser
        hotel pick and drop and excursion in shared boat.(national Park fees of 400 THB per person extra to be settled on spot)\n
Day 03 Bf at Hotel\n\t
            Half day Phuket City tour shared coach\n
Day 04 Bf at hotel.\n\t
        Drop at Phuket  Airport private coach, fly for Bangkok on arrival transfers to Bangkok Hotel Arnoma grand  in private coach.
        1  unit of Junior suite 42  sq mts room area with Bf factored at for 2 nights.\n
Day 05 Bf at Hotel\n\t
              Full day safari world or Dream world tour includes lunch with transfers on shared coach.\n
Day 06 Bf at hotel\n\t
        Entry to Sea life Aquarium and Madame Tussauds. Close to hotel no transfers factored hence.\n\t
        Evening drop at Airport.\n\n
Includes:\n
Accommodation for 5 nights with Bf\n
Airport Pick and Drop in private.\n
Sightseeing as mentioned</string>
    <string name="title_layout_help">Help\'s here</string>
    <string name="number_of_adults">Number of Adults</string>
    <string name="rooms_required">Rooms required</string>
</resources>

